<form version="1.1" script="datalocation.js" stylesheet="settings.css,common.css">
    <label>Data Location</label>
    <description>Use the panels below to load network telemetry into the Analytics Engine for processing.</description>

    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>
                <div id="data-tabs"></div>
                <div id="data-tabs-content">
                    <div id="data-logs-dns"></div>
                    <div id="data-logs-ip"></div>
                    <div id="data-logs-http"></div>
                    <div id="data-logs-tls"></div>
                    <div id="data-logs-dhcp"></div>
                    <div id="data-logs-vpn"></div>
                </div>
            </html>
        </panel>
        <panel>
            <html>
                <div id="data-alerts">
                    <h2 class="panel-title">Alert location</h2>
                    <p>The application stores alerts within the main index by default. To optimize performance,
                    you can store alerts within a particular index.</p>
                    <div id="data-alerts-index" class="data-location-box"></div>

                    <h2 class="panel-title">Alert data health</h2>
                    <p>The status bar below reports whether alerts are being stored correctly. If you make
                    changes to your configuration, this may take a few minutes to update.</p>
                    <div id="data-alerts-status"></div>
                </div>

                <div id="data-destinations">
                    <h2 class="panel-title">Summary Indexing</h2>
                    <p>
                        AlphaSOC can summarize the destinations within your telemetry on a daily basis, and index
                        that data within Splunk. This feature enables teams to quickly retrospectively search historic
                        data for particular IP addresses and FQDNs. Use the settings below to enable and configure this feature.
                    </p>
                    <div id="data-destinations-enabled" class="data-location-box"></div>
                    <h2 class="panel-title">Summary data location</h2>
                    <p>
                        Use the text input below to define the destination index for summary data.
                    </p>
                    <div id="data-destinations-index" class="data-location-box"></div>
                    <h2 class="panel-title">Summary data health</h2>
                    <p>
                        The status bar below reports whether summary data is being stored correctly. If you make
                        changes to your configuration, this may take a few minutes to update.
                    </p>
                    <div id="data-destinations-status"></div>
                </div>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
    <row>
        <panel>
            <html>
                <h2 class="panel-title">Download application logs</h2>
                <p>The application expects CIM compliant network events and should automatically
                ingest data. If you experience difficulties during setup and configuration, use the
                button below to download application logs, and submit the file to
                <a href="mailto:support@alphasoc.com">support@alphasoc.com</a> for assistance.</p>
                <div id="data-logs-export"></div>
            </html>
        </panel>
    </row>
</form>
